Guide to the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, records of the dean
1916-2013
RU 948
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
129.75
The records consist of subject files, reports, memoranda and meeting minutes documenting the departments, fellows, faculty, and general administration of the Yale Graduate School of Arts and Sciences. The records include the files of deans Wilbur L. Cross (1916-1930), Edgar S. Furniss (1930-1950), Hartley Simpson (1956-1961), John Perry Miller (1961-1969), Donald Wayne Taylor (1969-1975), Jaroslav Jan Pelikan (1973-1974, acting dean and 1975-1978), Keith Stewart Thomson (1979-1986), Thomas Applequist (1993-1997) and Lynn Cooley (2014-present).
Yale University. Graduate School
Cross, Wilbur L. (Wilbur Lucius), 1862-1948
Furniss, Edgar S. (Edgar Stephenson), 1918-1966
Miller, John Perry, 1911-1997
Pelikan, Jaroslav, 1923-2006
Simpson, Hartley, 1900-1967
Taylor, Donald Wayne, 1919-
Thomson, Keith Stewart
Cooley, Lynn
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 25-A (YRG 25-A), Central records and records of the dean of the Yale Graduate School.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of subject files, reports, memoranda and meeting minutes documenting the departments, fellows, faculty, and general administration of the Yale Graduate School of Arts and Sciences. The records include the files of deans Wilbur L. Cross (1916-1930), Edgar S. Furniss (1930-1950), Hartley Simpson (1956-1961), John Perry Miller (1961-1969), Donald Wayne Taylor (1969-1975), Jaroslav Jan Pelikan (1973-1974, acting dean and 1975-1978), Keith Stewart Thomson (1979-1986), Thomas Applequist (1993-1997) and Lynn Cooley (2014-present).
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Universities and colleges -- Graduate work; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Graduate work; Yale University. Graduate School
- Records of John Perry Miller as dean, circa 1950-1969; Accession 2004-A-058
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - Industrial Administration Project, 1953-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 2)
  - Information Theory, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Non-Western International Studies, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Italian, 1949-1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Latin-American Center (Ford), 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Linguistics, Dept. of, 1954-1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Mathematics, 1954-1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Medical Sciences, 1959-1962 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Medieval Studies, 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Mental Health Nursing, 1953-1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Microbiology, 1954-1963 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Molecular Biology and Biophysics, 1956-1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Music, 1953-1967 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures, 1956-1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Nursing- M.S. in Nursing Program, 1956-1963 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Peabody Museum, 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Philosophy, 1951-1967 (Box 1, Folder 18 - 19)
  - Physics, 1950-1967 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Political Science
    - 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 21 - 23)
    - 1951-1962 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Psychology, 1952-1967 (Box 2, Folder 25 - 26)
  - Public Health, 1953-1964 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Religion, 1949-1964 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Religious Studies, Department of, 1961-1967 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Romance Languages and Literatures, 1958-1962 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Russian Foreign Policy Conference, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Social Science Interdisciplinary Program, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Sociology, 1957-1967 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Southeast Asia Studies, 1956-1962 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Spanish, 1957-1964 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Special Registration, Division of, 1953-1959 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Statistics, 1953-1965 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Zoology, 1956-1962 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Summer Programs, 1962-1968 (Box 2, Folder 39 - 40)
  - Summer Calendar, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Departmental Annual Reports, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 42 - 43)
  - Departmental Quotas, 1961-1966 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Administrative Sciences, Dept. of, 1965 - 1966 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Anthropology, Dept. of, 1954-1964 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Archeology, Committee on, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Astronomy, Dept. of, 1958-1965 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Biology, Dept. of, 1961-1967 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Botany, 1957-1962 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Chemistry, Dept. of, 1951-1964 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Classics, Dept. of, 1959-1966 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Conservation, 1953-1960 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - East and South Asian Languages and Literatures, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Economics, Department of, 1951-1968 (Box 3, Folder 55 - 58)
  - Pakistan Institute of Development Economics, 1964-1969 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Economic History, Department of, 1961-1965 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, 1961-1968 (Box 3, Folder 61 - 63)
  - School of Engineering, Student Affairs, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Engineering Departments (Former), 1946-1963 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - English, 1952-1966 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health, 1962-1967 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Far Eastern Languages, Institute of, 1961-1966 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Foreign Area Studies, 1958-1962 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Forestry, 1955-1966 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - French, 1948-1964 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Geography, Department of, 1948-1964 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Geology, 1953-1966 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1954-1966 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Handbook Department of History, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - History, Department of, 1951-1967 (Box 4, Folder 76 - 77)
  - History of Art, 1958-1967 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - History of Science and Medicine, 1954-1967 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Indic and Far Eastern Languages, 1958-1963 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - A.G.S. Fellowship - Assistantship code, 1947-1967 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Assistants in Instruction and Teaching Associates Stipends, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Assistantships in Instruction on Research, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Auditing Courses - Faculty Wives Staff, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Auditing Courses by Students not Regularly Enrolled in Yale, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Board of Permanent Officers, 1959-1967 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Board of Permanent Officers - G.S. Reorganization, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - The "Brain Drain", 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Bursary Assignments - Graduate School, 1961-1967 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - COGS - Committee on Accreditation (See Transfer File), 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Colloquium (Issues in Higher Education), 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Dean's Diary, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Dean's Fund - Agency Account
    - 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Dean's Discretionary Fund 8700-1935-1976825, 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Dissertation Readers - Outside, 1950-1966 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Dissertation Readers - Selection of, 1961-1964 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Directives - General, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - English-Speaking Union Chicago Award, 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Executive Committee, Graduate School, 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - English - Remedial Language Course, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Fellowships, Report on, 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Fellowships - General Appropriations, 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Fellowship Information - General, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Financial Aid Policies, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Financing of Graduate Students Survey, Office of Education, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Foreign Service Officers File, Dept. of State, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Frauds, 1950-1955 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Graduate School Association, 1964-1967 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Graduate School Association - List of Contributors, etc., 1961-1965 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Graduate School, 1952-1958 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Graduate School Dormitory Regulations, Room Rentals, 1960-1964 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Graduate Student Teaching Assistants, 1963-1967 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Graduate Women's Dormitory, Committee on, 1957-1963 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Guggenheim Fellowships, 1957-1967 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - Helen Hadley Hall, 1958-1968 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Intensive Summer Studies Program, Harvard-Yale-Columbia, 1966-1968 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - ISSP Transfer File, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - International Student Center, 1961-1964 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - M.A. Degree Arguments, 1944-1965 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Master of Philosophy Degree, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Museum Fellows Training, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - NSF, WW and Danforth FPS. Lists, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Teacher Placement Office, 1959-1965 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - PH.D 1961 Anniversary, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - PH.D. Committee
    - Biological Sciences, 1960-1962 (Box 5, Folder 131)
    - Humanities, 1951-1963 (Box 5, Folder 132)
    - Physical Sciences, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 133)
    - Social Sciences, 1943-1962 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Division of Sciences, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Division of Social Sciences, 1951-1964 (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Statistics, 1940-1968 (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - Student Housing, 1954-1967 (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - Teaching Assistantships, 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - University Council Comm. on the Graduate School, 1962-1967 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Juniper Lounge, 1933-1965 (Box 5, Folder 141)
- Records of the dean of the graduate school, 1963-1983; Accession 2004-A-113
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2018
  - Yale Alumni Fund (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AYA (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Assembly of AYA (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Board (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Association of American Universities (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - AAU (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - AAU Meeting in Washington, 1971 October 26 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - AAU Meeting in Washington, 1978 January 30 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Association of Graduate Schools (A.G.S.) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - AGS Nominating Committee (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - AGS Mailing List (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Graduate School Alumni Fund
    - Letters (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Gifts for Other than Loans (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Reports (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Department Letters (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Restricted Gifts (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Letters to Departments - Re: Distribution of Funds (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Future of Alumni Fund (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Affirmative Action (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Admit Letters, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 20 - 21)
  - Admissions Tabulations (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Beta House (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Beta House - Agreement between Covington Trust and Yale (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Beta House Department Alterations - Budget Requests (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Budget Office (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Commencement Program, Yale University - First Copy, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Commencement, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Commencement, Graduate School, 1976 May 17 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Contingent Repayment Contract (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Culler Report (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Committee on Faculty Research Grants, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Concilium on International and Area Studies (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Conference of Academic Deans, Duke University, 1973 June 24 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Conference of Academic Deans, Northwestern Univ, 1972 June 25-27 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Conference of Academic Deans, Univ of Rochester, 1971 June 24-26 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - CGS - Council of Graduate Schools (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - CGS Executive Committee (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Wilbur Cross Medal (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Wilbur Cross Committee Meeting, 1974 December 9 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Wilbur Cross Medal, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Wilbur Cross Medal Citations (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Nominations for Wilbur Cross Medal (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Wilbur Cross Medal, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Wilbur Cross Medal, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Wilbur Cross Medal, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Joint Bachelor's-Master's Degree (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Departmental Proposals for Reinstatement of M.A. and M.S. (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Reestablishment of M.A. and M.S. Degrees (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Reestablishment of M.A. and M.S. Degrees (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - GPSFAS - Graduate and Professional School Financial Aid Service (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Steering Committee of the GPSFAS, 1972 September 29 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Enrollment (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Fellowships (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Junior Faculty Fellowships (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Prize Teaching Fellowships, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Nominations for Prize Teaching Fellowships, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Yale Government Fellowships Program (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Ford Report (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Application for Title VI NDEA Fellowships (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Governance Commission (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Graduate School Reps. On the Study Commission on Governance (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - YGP (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Graduate-Professional Student Senate (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Graduate Student Senate (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Graduate Student Center (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - GPSS Teaching Fellows (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - GPSS Task Force on Fellowships and Financial Aid (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - GPSS, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - GRE Board, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Proposal for a Study of Quality in Doctoral Education (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - GRE Board (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - GRE Witkin Study (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Replies (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - GRE Volume (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - GRE Research Committee (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Humanities Institute (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Office of Institutional Research (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Office of Institutional Research Meeting of, 1972 May 10 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Library (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Meyer Report - Urban Studies at Yale (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Military Science (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - News Bureau (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Office of Teacher Placement (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Positions (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - President's Office (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Psychology (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Residential College Seminars (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Committee on Summer Programs (Box 5, Folder 97 - 98)
  - Summer Programs, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Tuition Postponement Option (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Stanford University (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Stanford University Appointments Procedures (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Women (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Analysis of Female Yale Ph.D. holders in higher education, 1945-1971 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Women's Liaison Committee (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Yale College (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Yale College - Admissions Policy (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Degree Committees -, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Urban Studies (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Ad Hoc Program in Urban and Environmental Studies (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Leaves of Absence Approved for 1973-1974, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Leaves of Absence Withdrawn or Disapproved (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Leaves of Absence Approved for 1972-1973, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Postdoctoral Education at Yale (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Postdoctoral Fellow Policies (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Student Problems
  - Ad Hoc Comm.- Dissertation of Catherine Ricciuti (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Summer Term Committee (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - President Giamatti (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Memoranda - Provost's Office, 1963-1971 (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - President Brewster (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - Memoranda - Provost's Office, 1972-1975 (Box 6, Folder 128 - 129)
  - Charles H. Taylor, Jr. (Box 6, Folder 130)
  - Hanna H. Gray (Box 6, Folder 131)
  - George D. Langdon, Jr. - Deputy Provost (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - Jacqueline W. Mintz - Associate Provost (Box 6, Folder 134)
  - Dean Taylor - HGS (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - Summer Term Committee - Dean Taylor 112 HGS (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Honoraria Paid (Box 6, Folder 137 - 138)
  - Joint Meeting of the Boards of Permanent Officers
  - 1977 May 10 (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - 1977 Apr 7 (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - Senior Appointments Committee Meeting Physical Sciences, 1978 April 25 (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - Joint Meeting of the Boards, 1976 December 17 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Meetings - Junior and Term Appointments Committee (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - Senior Appointments Committee Meeting Social Sciences
    - 1979 May 2 (Box 6, Folder 144)
    - 1979 Apr 11 (Box 6, Folder 145)
    - 1979 Mar 28 (Box 6, Folder 146)
    - 1979 Feb 21 (Box 6, Folder 147)
    - 1979 Feb 14 (Box 6, Folder 148)
    - 1978 Dec 13 (Box 6, Folder 149)
    - 1978 Nov 8 (Box 6, Folder 150)
    - 1978 Oct 11 (Box 6, Folder 151)
    - 1978 Apr 26 (Box 6, Folder 152)
    - 1978 Apr 19 (Box 6, Folder 153)
    - 1978 Apr 12 (Box 6, Folder 154)
    - 1978 Mar 8 (Box 6, Folder 155)
    - 1978 Mar 1 (Box 6, Folder 156)
    - 1977 Nov 16 (Box 6, Folder 157)
  - Senior Appointments Comm. Meeting Biological Sciences
    - 1978 Apr 24 (Box 6, Folder 158)
    - 1978 Apr 3 (Box 6, Folder 159)
    - 1978 Jan 23 (Box 6, Folder 160)
    - 1979 Mar 5 (Box 6, Folder 161)
    - 1979 May 9 (Box 6, Folder 162)
    - 1979 Apr 2 (Box 6, Folder 163)
    - 1978 Dec 18 (Box 6, Folder 164)
  - Senior Appointments Comm. Meeting Physical Sciences (Box 6, Folder 165)
    - 1979 May 15 (Box 6, Folder 166)
    - 1979 Apr 24 (Box 6, Folder 167)
    - 1979 Apr 3 (Box 6, Folder 168)
    - 1979 Feb 27 (Box 6, Folder 169)
    - 1978 Nov 28 (Box 6, Folder 170)
    - 1978 Dec 12 (Box 6, Folder 171)
  - Senior Appointments Comm. Meeting Humanities (Box 6, Folder 172)
    - 1976 May 6
    - 1977 Sep 28 (Box 6, Folder 173)
  - Senior Appointments Comm. Meeting Physical Sciences
    - 1978 Apr 11 (Box 7, Folder 174)
    - 1978 Feb 28 (Box 7, Folder 175)
    - 1977 Nov 15 (Box 7, Folder 176)
  - Senior Appointments Comm. Meeting Humanities
    - 1979 Apr 26 (Box 7, Folder 177)
    - 1979 Apr 12 (Box 7, Folder 178)
    - 1979 Apr 5 (Box 7, Folder 179)
    - 1979 Mar 8 (Box 7, Folder 180)
    - 1979 Feb 15 (Box 7, Folder 181)
    - 1979 Feb 8 (Box 7, Folder 182)
    - 1978 Dec 14 (Box 7, Folder 183)
    - 1978 Apr 27 (Box 7, Folder 184)
    - 1978 Apr 20 (Box 7, Folder 185)
    - 1978 Apr 6 (Box 7, Folder 186)
    - 1978 Mar 3 (Box 7, Folder 187)
    - 1977 Dec 1 (Box 7, Folder 188)
  - Senior Appointments Comm. Meetings Social Sciences, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 189)
  - Senior Appointments Comm. Meetings Biological Sciences, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 190)
  - Senior Appointments Comm. Meetings Humanities, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 191)
  - Senior Appointments Comm. Meetings Physical Sciences, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 192)
  - Junior Appointments Committee Meeting
    - 1977 May 11 (Box 7, Folder 193)
    - 1977 Apr 4 (Box 7, Folder 194)
    - 1977 Feb 21 (Box 7, Folder 195)
    - 1976 May 7 (Box 7, Folder 196)
  - Joint Meeting of the Boards of Permanent Officers
    - 1976 May 6 (Box 7, Folder 197)
    - 1976 Apr 23 (Box 7, Folder 198)
    - 1975 Dec 4 (Box 7, Folder 199)
  - Senior Appointments Comm. Meeting Humanities
    - 1976 Apr 29 (Box 7, Folder 200)
    - 1976 Apr 22 (Box 7, Folder 201)
    - 1976 Apr 1 (Box 7, Folder 202)
    - 1975 Oct 16 (Box 7, Folder 203)
  - Senior Appointments Comm. Meeting Physical Sciences
    - 1976 Apr 20 (Box 7, Folder 204)
    - 1976 Apr 13 (Box 7, Folder 205)
  - Request for Reconsideration (Box 7, Folder 206)
  - Senior Appointments Comm. Meeting Physical Sciences
    - 1976 Mar 30 (Box 7, Folder 207)
    - 1976 Feb 17 (Box 7, Folder 208)
    - 1975 Nov 18 (Box 7, Folder 209)
  - Senior Appointments Comm. Meeting Social Sciences
    - 1976 Apr 21 (Box 7, Folder 210)
    - 1976 Apr 7 (Box 7, Folder 211)
    - 1976 Feb 25 (Box 7, Folder 212)
    - 1976 Apr 19 (Box 7, Folder 213)
    - 1976 Mar 22 (Box 7, Folder 214)
    - 1975 Oct 20 (Box 7, Folder 215)
    - 1976 Feb 16 (Box 7, Folder 216)
    - 1975 May 9 (Box 7, Folder 217)
  - Junior Appointments Committee Meeting
    - 1980 Feb 25 (Box 7, Folder 218)
    - 1979 Dec 10 (Box 7, Folder 219)
    - 1978 Feb 27 (Box 7, Folder 220)
    - 1977 Dec 5 (Box 7, Folder 221)
  - Junior and Term Appointments Committee Meeting, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 222)
  - Joint Committees on Appointments, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 223)
  - Junior Appointments Committee Meeting
    - 1979 Apr 12 (Box 7, Folder 224)
    - 1979 May 7 (Box 7, Folder 225)
    - 1979 Apr 9 (Box 7, Folder 226)
    - 1979 Feb 26 (Box 7, Folder 227)
    - 1978 Dec 18 (Box 7, Folder 228)
  - Junior and Term Appointments Committee Meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 229)
  - Joint Meeting of the Boards of Permanent Officers
    - 1975 May 8 (Box 7, Folder 230)
    - 1975 Feb 27 (Box 7, Folder 231)
    - 1975 Jan 30 (Box 7, Folder 232)
    - 1974 Dec 12 (Box 7, Folder 233)
    - 1974 Oct 3 (Box 7, Folder 234)
  - Senior Appointments Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 235)
  - Senior Appointments Comm. Meeting Humanities
    - 1975 May 1 (Box 7, Folder 236)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 237)
    - 1975 Apr 17 (Box 7, Folder 238)
    - 1975 Apr 3 (Box 7, Folder 239)
    - 1975 Mar 27 (Box 7, Folder 240)
    - 1975 Feb 6 (Box 7, Folder 241)
    - 1974 Dec 5 (Box 7, Folder 242)
    - 1974 Nov 21 (Box 7, Folder 243)
  - Senior Appointments Comm. Meetings Physical Sciences
    - 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 244)
    - 1975 May 6 (Box 7, Folder 245)
    - 1975 Jan 14 (Box 7, Folder 246)
    - 1974 Dec 3 (Box 7, Folder 247)
  - Senior Appointments Comm. Meetings Social Sciences
    - 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 248)
    - 1975 May 7 (Box 7, Folder 249)
    - 1976 Apr 28 (Box 7, Folder 250)
    - 1975 Apr 16 (Box 7, Folder 251)
    - 1975 Feb 19 (Box 7, Folder 252)
    - 1975 Jan 22 (Box 7, Folder 253)
    - 1974 Nov 24 (Box 7, Folder 254)
  - Senior Appointments Comm. Meeting Physical Sciences, 1975 May 27 (Box 7, Folder 255)
  - Senior Appointments Comm. Meeting Social Sciences, 1974 December 4 (Box 7, Folder 256)
  - Senior Appointments Comm. Meetings Biological Sciences
    - 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 257)
    - 1975 May 12 (Box 7, Folder 258)
    - 1975 Apr 29 (Box 7, Folder 259)
    - 1975 Apr 14 (Box 7, Folder 260)
    - 1975 Feb 3 (Box 7, Folder 261)
  - Department Memoranda on Tenable Minority Faculty Members (Box 7, Folder 262)
  - Search for Faculty in College Seminars (Box 7, Folder 263)
  - Senior Appointments Committee Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 264)
  - Search Letters, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 265 - 266)
  - Search for Faculty in Departments (Box 7, Folder 267)
  - Meeting of Advisory Comm. - 11/19 and Executive Comm. - 11/22 (Box 7, Folder 268)
  - Minutes of the Advisory Committee of the Graduate School, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 269)
  - Degree Committees (Box 7, Folder 270)
  - Degree Committees (Box 8, Folder 271)
  - Degree Committees, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 272)
  - Financial Information - Paul E. Darlington (Box 8, Folder 273)
  - Committee on the College and the Graduate School (Box 8, Folder 274)
  - Committee on the College and the Graduate School (Box 8, Folder 275)
  - Degree Committees, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 276)
  - Committee on the College and the Graduate School (Box 8, Folder 277)
  - Committee on Summer Term (Box 8, Folder 278)
  - Yale College Committee on the Future (Box 8, Folder 279)
  - Dean Garner (Box 8, Folder 280)
  - Dean Garner - Executive Committee on the Graduate School, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 281)
  - Memoranda - Dean Bockelman (Box 8, Folder 282)
  - Dean Bockelman - Memoranda to Chairmen and DGS's, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 283)